(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-08-02T22:14:44.592929",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
The concert will be starting soon.
Attention - For Visitors
Attention For Visitors
The concert will be starting soon.
2nd Round of Concert Merch Sales
Attention For Visitors
The concert will be starting soon.
KFP! KFP! KFP! KFP!
Thank you all so much for coming to...
Takanashi Kiara and Ninomae Ina'nis's 1st concert DRAW to DAWN!
Kikkeriki!
Yep, I am Takanashi Kiara, and...
Good morning, afternoon, evening, everyone! It's Ninomae Ina'nis!
That's right, it's finally time for our concert! Is everyone hyped?
Before we kick things off, we have some important safety rules and house guidelines to go over.
First, photography and the use of any recording equipment are strictly prohibited during the performance.
Also, the venue is smoke-free, so please refrain from smoking inside.
But what if I'm smoking hot?
Minus, Kiara!
If you start feeling unwell at any point, please don't push yourself, just reach out to the nearest staff member for help and hydrate!
For everyone's safety, please avoid any dangerous or disruptive behavior.
This includes moshing...
No moshing! I mean it!
Moshing, diving, sitting on shoulders, jumping excessively, or throwing objects towards the stage.
Climbing onto the stage, intentionally blocking the aisles, or rushing toward the front is also, surprise, not allowed!
Please refrain from disruptive shouting, erratic lightstick movements, or any extreme motions that might interfere with the experience of those around you.
Be considerate!
If you don't follow the instructions of our staff or the venue staff, you may be asked to leave the venue.
Yes, please keep in mind that the venue organizers, performers,
and staff cannot be held responsible for any accidents, equipment damage, or trouble caused by failing to follow instructions.
Additionally, any costs for damages resulting from ignoring these rules will be the responsibility of the person involved. So be careful, guys, okay?
There are cameras in the venue for filming and photography today...
...and you might appear in footage or photos.
These may be used for promotional purposes later on, so please keep that in mind.
Y'all are looking cute!
And finally... big news! Today's concert will be in two parts!
There's a part for Kiara, and a part for me, so please look forward to both of them!
All right, that is it for the rules! The show is about to begin, so get ready!
Bye-bye! Bye-bye! See you soon!
Tako-tori! Tako-tori! Tako-tori! Tako-tori!
Oi! Oi! Oi! Oi!
DRAWN TO DAWN
リバ！ リバ！
Liba! Liba!
Love & Glory! Love & Glory!
リバ！ リバ！
Liba! Liba!
オイ！ オイ！ オイ！
Oi! Oi! Oi!
リバ！ リバ！
Liba! Liba!
Love & Glory! Love & Glory!
Enlightened by the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on insanity
It's clear to me they still can't see
I'm just a normal girl
Empowered by the ancient one's call
We're gonna be pun-stoppable, we're not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical
Adventures lie in wait (Give me a one-eight)
1, 8, タコダチ 1, 8, タコダチ
1, 8, Takodachi 1, 8, Takodachi
Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina
俺のInaの世界線 守るためにタコになろう！
Let's become takos to protect my timeline with Ina!
1, 8, タコダチ 1, 8, タコダチ
1, 8, Takodachi 1, 8, Takodachi
Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina, Ina
いいタコになりますように Insanityで踊りましょう！
May we become good takos! Let's dance in insanity!
Think of all that you can be
We're talking evolution, leave it all to me
Maybe just a touch of purple ink, what ya think?
It's a song you can't ignore
The ancient ones are calling you to be so much more
Just put your hand in mine and be reborn in a blink
Tell me what those legs are for? (俺のイナ運ぶためです！)
Tell me what those legs are for? (To carry my Ina!)
You could use six more (感謝感謝！ありがたい！)
You could use six more (Thanks so much! I'm grateful!)
We could all get matching ears (They aren't really ears though, eh?)
Sleepy eyes to fight your fears (例えばInaいないの世界！ Alright)
Sleepy eyes to fight your fears (For example, a world without Ina! Alright)
Listen to my song, am I striking a chord with you?
Stringing you along, so don't let me get bored of you
Eighty million strong and we've still got some more to do
Everybody shout, "World domination!"
Can I bank on your emotion? Do I have you invested?
I don't wanna hear you say that you're not interested
Your unwavering devotion isn't all I've requested
Do you care? Are you aware that you're my dearest creations?
おやおや A cute little Takodachi found its way here
Oh my, a cute little Takodachi found its way here
Experimentation might be necessary
Takos, we have to cook (いいタコだちの作り方！)
Takos, we have to cook (How to make good Takodachis!)
ひっくり返して丸くして (Nice)
Flip them over and make them round (Nice)
コロコロまわして焦がさずに (いいね！)
Roll them around without burning them (Good!)
外はカリッと中ふわふわ
Crispy on the outside, fluffy on the inside
できたらソースでさあいただき！
When they're done, add sauce and dig in!
And by the powers that be
The ruler of a world run on insanity
It's clear to me they still can't see
I'm just a normal girl
Empowered by the ancient one's call
We're gonna be pun-stoppable, we're not a cult
Nonsensical and nautical
Adventures lie in wait
DRAWN TO DAWN
KikiRiki! Welcome to Day 1 of Drawn to Dawn!
I am Takanashi Kiara! Let's get it on!
瞬く星の揺りかご
The twinkling cradle of stars,
欠けたセリフをつなぎ合わせたメモリー
memories linked together from missing words...
聖なる従者が歌う 神魔の理
The sacred servant sings of divine and demonic truths.
祈りに耳を澄ませ
Listen closely to the prayers.
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice...
荒ぶる言葉 傷を穿つ
Wild words pierce through the wounds.
焔降り注ぐ空に 身を焦がして
Scorch yourself beneath a sky raining flames.
刻まれた赤き紋章
An engraved red crest...
数多重なる試練も 生き抜いてみせる
I will survive through countless stacking trials!
I will live to keep on fighting till the dawn
Louder!
たとえば先の見えない ゼロの境界 迷い込んだとしても
Even if I stray into a boundary of zero with an unseen future,
何度も繰り返される 虚構の終焉 そこに残った Answer
in the repeatedly returning end of fiction, the Answer remaining there...
Don't break, I will never give up. Don't break, 抗ったとしても
Don't break, I will never give up. Don't break, even if I resist,
消せない強さは 時の標
this indestructible strength is a beacon through time!
灰が舞い上がる大地 身をくぐらせ
Passing through a land where ashes dance,
この夜明けの中 目を覚ます 刃交じる Valkyrie
awakening in the midst of this dawn, a Valkyrie with clashing blades!
交わした契りは Lies and Truth 燻る情熱
The exchanged vows are lies and truth, a smoldering passion...
I've been trying to find my destiny
But they keep pushing and pulling me astray
If I go, run, what awaits me in the dark?
Could you tell me please where I need to go?
Tell me, I can hear it clearly
Tell me, 声なき声に
Tell me, to the voiceless voice...
みなぎる決意は 影を払う
Overflowing determination dispels the shadows!
焔降り注ぐ空に 身を焦がして
Scorch yourself beneath a sky raining flames.
刻まれた赤き紋章
An engraved red crest...
数多重なる試練も 生き抜いてみせる
I will survive through countless stacking trials!
Raging flames, 東を照らす Luminous and in the next, next night too
Raging flames illuminating the east, luminous, and in the next, next night too...
I promise I will find you
Clap your hands!
Lying down on the floor
Late night and you don't know, don't know, don't know what to do
Hard to tell what's wrong, what's right
If yes or no, don't know, don't know what to do
The storm hits hard and you're losing the way
Just take a chance and dance in the rain
'Cause you got the key, never throw it away
Don't forget, don't forget what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So go ahead and do it, do it, if you want it, let's get to it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop! Just go your own way!
So don't be afraid, trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up! And never be afraid!
Gotta make it hot like a volcano, strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table to the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait, start a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop! Just go your own way!
We ain't looking back, take the fast lane now
In the driver's seat strapped, they just gasp out loud
Going so fast that it shouldn't be allowed
That's how we like it, you heard what I said
Get out of your head
Life is only what you make it
You're gonna be okay
So take a step and move it, move it, 'less you try you won't get through it
Everybody's gonna know your name
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop! Just go your own way!
So don't be afraid, trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up! And never be afraid!
Let go of the past tonight
Choose the future only you define
Even when the flames burn too bright, you're alive, from the ashes you rise
Clap! Clap! Clap!
Everybody!
'Cause sparks light the flame, turn the dark of the night into day
Don't stop, don't stop! Just go your own way!
So don't be afraid, trust your heart, keep your head in the game
Keep up, keep up! And never be afraid!
Gotta make it hot like a volcano, strike a match and burn it up
Kick your feet against the table to the beat of your own drum
Sparks light the flame, so don't wait, start a fire today
Don't stop, don't stop! Just go your own way!
Kikkeriki!
Hello! Welcome everybody to Takanashi Kiara and hololive English's 1st ever concert, Connect the World!
I can hear you guys so clearly, and I can see you guys so clearly!
Hi everybody! Hi, hi!
Oh my god, we're in Los Angeles!
So we started off with the iconic and classic songs of mine, Hinotori and SParks!
Don't we love those songs? Was that hype?
Yeah! You guys know, like Hinotori was my first ever original song to put out, and...
...yeah, it was like the beginning of my music...
...musical history,
my musical journey,
and it's a song that means a lot to me.
And it's just so hype. It was also the first ever...
...time that I appeared in 3D, I think, long time ago
at Fes in Japan, right? Remember?
Good times! Yeah!
Thank you so much for cheering so loudly! You did so well!
Yeah!
I have been training so hard the past months in the gym,
trying to get stamina for this day,
because I think I learned about...
...learned and relearned about 20 choreographies!
Crazy, right?
Damn, that was a lot of work.
But finally the day has come to show it off to all of you!
I want to say hi, by the way,
to all the live viewers worldwide!
There's so many cinemas showing this concert right now.
Hello, world!
Can you hear me? I wonder if I can hear them.
Can I hear them over the continents?
Well, that's you guys!
But I think I can hear them, yeah!
Also, there's stream girls watching on YouTube right now, like Ollie and all the EN members!
Hi! Thank you!
So excited!
I have to give a little bit of an announcement from my side, actually.
Because it's very important, it has to be in the free part, because everybody needs to hear this.
My new album, Vogelfrei, you got it, right?
Thank you!
But in case you didn't, a second round of album sales has begun!
Yeah! So if you missed it previously or you want a new copy, starting from Saturday, March 28th, at 11 PM...
...I don't know which timezone.
Who knows, we'll find out, probably JST.
You will be able to order Vogelfrei again! So please, everybody, order Vogelfrei!
So far, the songs that I performed up until now were not even from Vogelfrei, but don't worry, I'm squeezing everything in that I can.
Yeah!
Okay, guys.
You're probably aware of this,
but the free part usually ends after an MC.
But free part, you only had two songs!
Nah, nah, nah. Don't worry, I told staff,
"We can't be having that! I want the free part to have a little bit more!" Yeah!
So it will continue a little bit more, and then it will cut before the end of our MC, so just so you know.
And then, once it cuts, please...
...streaming tickets are available still in the description and in the pinned comment!
Probably there!
Yeah, so make sure to get your ticket, because what you haven't even seen yet is my colleague,
Ninomae Ina'nis, right?
Yeah, yeah, yeah! The concert is split in half, so today you only have me in the free part.
But later, if you want to see more of Wawa and Ina, go get streaming tickets! Yeah!
Okay!
So with that, it is time to move on to many other songs.
All right.
Are you ready?
All right!
Here is the next song! Enjoy!
Passing by, the fair erased
I couldn't find
the reason why
Who I am, you couldn't know
Stuck in the ruins
My disillusion
In between fake reality
My own desire
keeps me young
Moving faster than the light can
I'm in the absence
I'm looking back
Did I lose my way?
I can't see the day
When I can reach you again, then can I let go?
I can hear your voice leading me through the void
Fade away to the grey
Eternally I'm walking by
the lives that flash before my eyes
Alone, the silence deafening,
still I'm reaching out to you
Connection sacrificed,
the lie I tell myself so I'll survive
One day, eventually the light,
it'll lead me back, do you see me?
Da da da da ooh, wa-wanderer!
Da da da da, I am the wanderer
I'm tired of the same song
Every day like it's on repeat
I need a risky breakdown
Oh, honey, the night is young
Don't need a steady, simple melody
Can you make it a little bit major?
Take me away like it's just the two of us
Unraveling, do you feel the music, baby?
Meet me underneath the strobe light, come alive
Moving my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing, feel a rush through me
心と心の音 合わせて Follow my heartbeat
Align the sounds of our hearts,
follow my heartbeat
パラパラパラパラパッパ リズム聴かせてあげる
Pa-ra-pa-ra-pa-ra-pa-pa,
I'll play the rhythm for you
心のエフェクターに 合わせて
Match it to the effector in your heart
Follow my heartbeat, crazy for your rhythm
I'm in a trance with the way that you're moving
You got me shining, glowing like a prism
That disco ball makes me wild,
don't care who's watching us
So, baby, meet me underneath
the strobe light, come alive
Moving my feet to something new
I don't need no drinks tonight
Give me that beat, get me dancing, feel a rush through me
Baby, can we dance until the daylight?
Crazy
Got this song on repeat, DO U?
The sneak peek part of the show has ended.
Thank you for watching.
無料パートは終了いたしました。ご視聴ありがとうございました！
The free preview part of the show has ended. Thank you for watching!